http://www.lasercentermd.com/privacy-policy-terms-of-service/

(410) 544-4600
Hit enter to search or ESC to close
Regions: Privacy PolicyYour privacy is important to us. It is Laser Center of Maryland’s policy to respect your privacy regarding any information we may collect from you across our website, http://lasercentermd.com/, and other sites we own and operate.We only ask for personal information when we truly need it to provide a service to you. We collect it by fair and lawful means, with your knowledge and consent. We also let you know why we’re collecting it and how it will be used.We only retain collected information for as long as necessary to provide you with your requested service. What data we store, we’ll protect within commercially acceptable means to prevent loss and theft, as well as unauthorised access, disclosure, copying, use or modification.We don’t share any personally identifying information publicly or with third-parties, except when required to by law.Our website may link to external sites that are not operated by us. Please be aware that we have no control over the content and practices of these sites, and cannot accept responsibility or liability for their respective privacy policies.You are free to refuse our request for your personal information, with the understanding that we may be unable to provide you with some of your desired services.Your continued use of our website will be regarded as acceptance of our practices around privacy and personal information. If you have any questions about how we handle user data and personal information, feel free to contact us.This policy is effective as of 19 March 2019.
COMPANY INFO484-A Ritchie Hwy Severna Park, MD 21146410-544-4600info@lasercentermd.com Site LinksBlogPayment and FinancingPatient Forms Learn about Testosterone Replacement Therapy and how it can change your life.© 2020 Laser Center MD. All Rights Reserved. Terms and Conditions | Privacy Policy. *Individual results may vary.
SpecialsDecember SpecialsAboutOur DoctorsOur StaffTestimonialsPayment and FinancingBlogCOSMETIC SURGERYFaceBlepharoplasty (Eyelid)EarlobeFaceliftDouble ChinSkin TighteningThermiRF – Facial & Body Skin TighteningHair Restoration & Transplant (Neograft)BodyCellulite TreatmentBrazilian Butt LiftFat GraftingBreast AugmentationSkin TighteningTummy TuckLiposuctionLaser LiposuctionBody SculptingChinAbdominal EtchingThermiTight Radio-frequencyBody SculptingNeck RejuvenationNonsurgical ProceduresThermiSmooth radio-frequencySkin TighteningSweat ReductionMiraDryLaser Skin TreatmentLaser Rejuvenation with PRPLaser Facial RejuvenationLaser Hand RejuvenationLaser Skin ResurfacingSkin CancerWrinklesMicrolaserpeelMole RemovalLaser Wart RemovalLaser Tattoo RemovalGenital Wart RemovalToe Nail FungusScar RemovalStretch Mark TreatmentFacial Spider Vein RemovalLeg Spider Vein RemovalRosacea TreatmentsNon-InvasiveSkin RejuvenationAcne TreatmentAcne Scar and Pit RemovalSun DamageSun Damage TreatmentsBroadband Light (BBL)Halo LaserSkin Discoloration, Melasma, Sun Damage, & Age SpotsWomen OnlyThermiva Vaginal RejuvenationLabial ReductionFat ReductionCool SculptingHairLaser Hair RemovalInjectablesDermal FillersWrinkle RemoverMen OnlyPearly Penile PapulesMale Testosterone Replacement Therapy (TRT)Hair Replacement & Transplant (NEOGRAFT)Male Breast Reduction (Gynecomastia)Medi-Spa ServicesBody Shaping & Skin TighteningWrinkle RemoverDermasweep MicrodermabrasionhydrafacialMicroLaserPeel (MLP)Level Skincare ProductsMicroneedlingRegenerating Skin NectarBefore & AfterHormonal ReplacementContactFree Consultation
